Power Scheme GUID: 692ee1d0-ffc2-4c47-91b3-2a4814f3964e  (AERO24_MODERATE_AGGRESSIVE_GAMING)
  Subgroup GUID: 54533251-82be-4824-96c1-47b60b740d00  (Processor power management)
    GUID Alias: SUB_PROCESSOR
    Power Setting GUID: 36687f9e-e3a5-4dbf-b1dc-15eb381c6863  (Processor energy performance preference policy)
      GUID Alias: PERFEPP
      Minimum Possible Setting: 0x00000000
      Maximum Possible Setting: 0x00000064
      Possible Settings increment: 0x00000001
      Possible Settings units: %
    Current AC Power Setting Index: 0x00000037
    Current DC Power Setting Index: 0x00000000

    Power Setting GUID: 75b0ae3f-bce0-45a7-8c89-c9611c25e100  (Maximum processor frequency)
      GUID Alias: PROCFREQMAX
      Minimum Possible Setting: 0x00000000
      Maximum Possible Setting: 0xffffffff
      Possible Settings increment: 0x00000001
      Possible Settings units: MHz
    Current AC Power Setting Index: 0x00000cb2
    Current DC Power Setting Index: 0x00000000

    Power Setting GUID: 893dee8e-2bef-41e0-89c6-b55d0929964c  (Minimum processor state)
      GUID Alias: PROCTHROTTLEMIN
      Minimum Possible Setting: 0x00000000
      Maximum Possible Setting: 0x00000064
      Possible Settings increment: 0x00000001
      Possible Settings units: %
    Current AC Power Setting Index: 0x00000005
    Current DC Power Setting Index: 0x00000064

    Power Setting GUID: 94d3a615-a899-4ac5-ae2b-e4d8f634367f  (System cooling policy)
      GUID Alias: SYSCOOLPOL
      Possible Setting Index: 000
      Possible Setting Friendly Name: Passive
      Possible Setting Index: 001
      Possible Setting Friendly Name: Active
    Current AC Power Setting Index: 0x00000001
    Current DC Power Setting Index: 0x00000001

    Power Setting GUID: bc5038f7-23e0-4960-96da-33abaf5935ec  (Maximum processor state)
      GUID Alias: PROCTHROTTLEMAX
      Minimum Possible Setting: 0x00000000
      Maximum Possible Setting: 0x00000064
      Possible Settings increment: 0x00000001
      Possible Settings units: %
    Current AC Power Setting Index: 0x00000063
    Current DC Power Setting Index: 0x00000064

    Power Setting GUID: be337238-0d82-4146-a960-4f3749d470c7  (Processor performance boost mode)
      GUID Alias: PERFBOOSTMODE
      Possible Setting Index: 000
      Possible Setting Friendly Name: Disabled
      Possible Setting Index: 001
      Possible Setting Friendly Name: Enabled
      Possible Setting Index: 002
      Possible Setting Friendly Name: Aggressive
      Possible Setting Index: 003
      Possible Setting Friendly Name: Efficient Enabled
      Possible Setting Index: 004
      Possible Setting Friendly Name: Efficient Aggressive
      Possible Setting Index: 005
      Possible Setting Friendly Name: Aggressive At Guaranteed
      Possible Setting Index: 006
      Possible Setting Friendly Name: Efficient Aggressive At Guaranteed
    Current AC Power Setting Index: 0x00000000
    Current DC Power Setting Index: 0x00000002

